



DAMNHAND.COM

ADAM@DAMNHAND.COM

HI I'M ADAM HANDERMANN

I'm a designer, skater, and musician living in Portland, Oregon. I'm passionate about my craft, art, and just making cool things. I've worked with brand such as Nike, Trail Butter, Pair of Theives, and Boss. I do branding, packaging, UI design, photography, and am continously learning new things. Feel free to get in touch if you want to chat!

WORK EXPERIENCE

February 2018 - Present

Nike

Graphic Designer

November 2017 - May 2018

Distortion LTD
Creative Director

April 2017 - October 2017

Tone Report Weekly Creative Director

January 2017 - March 2017

Pair of Thieves Junior Designer

August 2016 - November 2016

The Great Society
Graphic Design Intern

EDUCATION

August 2014 to May 2016

Associate Degree Modern College of Art and Design

August 2012 to May 2014

High School Diploma
Butler Tech Career Center

AWARDS

GD USA Student Work Award

Award for Cotton Craft Branding Graphic Design USA

GD USA Student Work Award

Award for Vans Seasonal Retail Graphic Design USA

AAF Dayton Hermes Award - Student Work

Award for Vans Seasonal Retail AAF Dayton

SKILLS

BRANDING

UX DESIGN

PACKAGE DESIGN

ILLUSTRATION

React, jQuery, Typography, HTML5, CSS, Photography, Print Design, UI Design, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Xd, Sketch